let questions=[
 	{
    numb: 1,
    question: "Look at this series: 2, 1, (1/2), (1/4), ... What number should come next?",
    answer: "(1/8)",
    options: ["(1/3)","(1/8)","(2/8)","(1/16)"]
  },
	{
    numb: 2,
    question: "Look at the series: 1.5, 2.3, 3.1, 3.9, ... What number should come next?",
    answer: "4.7",
    options: ["4.2","4.4","5.1","4.7"]
  },
	{
    numb: 3,
    question: "Look at the series: 544, 509, 474, 439, ... What number should come next?",
    answer: "404",
    options: ["404","414","420","445"]
  },
	{
    numb: 4,
    question: "Look at the series: 5.2, 4.8, 4.4, 4, ... What number should come next?",
    answer: "3.6",
    options: ["3","3.3","3.5","3.6"]
  },
	{
    numb: 5,
    question: "Look at the series: F2, __, D8, C16, B32, ... What number should fill the blank?",
    answer: "E4",
    options: ["A16","G4","E4","E3"]
  },
	{
    numb: 6,
    question: "Look at the series: 664, 332, 340, 170, ____, 89, ... What number should fill the blank?",
    answer: "178",
    options: ["85","97","109","178"]
  },
	{
    numb: 7,
    question: "Look at the series: J14, L16, __, P20, R22, ... What number should fill the blank?",
    answer: "N18",
    options: ["S24","N18","M18","T24"]
  },
	{
    numb: 8,
    question: "Look at the series: XXIV, XX, __, XII, VIII, ... What number should fill the blank?",
    answer: "XVI",
    options: ["XXII","XIII","XVI","IV"]
  },
	{
    numb: 9,
    question: "Look at the series: U32, V29, __, X23, Y20, ... What number should fill the blank?",
    answer: "W26",
    options: ["W26","W17","Z17","Z26"]
  },
	{
    numb: 10,
    question: "Look at the series: 0.15, 0.3, ____, 1.2, 2.4, ... What number should fill the blank?",
    answer: "0.6",
    options: ["4.8","0.006","0.6","0.9"]
  },
  ];
